Cute!
Thank you for watching!
Three, two, one.
Applause.
Are you free later tonight?
Would you like to come with me?
I've always wanted to talk to you, Mizuna-san.
Even after the rain has stopped, we're still having a chatting party!
Ready, set, go!
Even though it's raining, we're still talking about the rain
Rain Shaberu for short!
Applause!
Good evening, everyone, from the new Amemurashii channel!
Good evening.
We are the Raindrops.
Please come on in.
I'm a little late, folks, and I'm really not on time.
I'm sorry.
Not a bit.
But that's why you all look prettier than usual.
Why?
Why? Because, after all, we've been together all day.
From morning to night.
So we feel together as one and our faces are prettier.
It feels good.
Even though Mayo did it for you.
Yes, that's right.
Yes, so the title crown this time,
Mayuka was in charge of it.
Yes, I called Mizuna this time.
Yes, please.
I really like the feeling.
I'm going to continue to be in the whole
I would like to invest
And to give you a compliment.
I will continue to wear it with care.
What would you say this is?
Do you recommend it?
No, sir.
These words...
Take it in stride.
Yes, sir.
So, thank you.
This is the part of the title call that I've always wanted to talk to you about who you are,
Pick one of you who tweeted me your thoughts on the candy talk,
We will be waiting for that person's name.
So please tweet us your impressions of the band with the hashtag Ameshaberu in katakana. Thank you very much.
Please do so.
A! A! Aah! Microphone test!
Uh-uh, kana-tsuzu-se,
Maybe it's a cell phone shot already, right? Like before.
Audio.
It's louder.
It's bigger! Then it's okay.
Then please spacha.
I'll say in a loud voice, "Thank you very much, Mizuna-san.
Thank you, Mizuna-san!
I'm so glad you're here!
Thank you!
This is Yae, I want to try Mr. Dodatu's Strawie Ponderingo candy which will be on sale on June 14!
I will enjoy it!
We all said it, right?
Let's eat all four kinds.
I want to eat them.
From Yusuke. Nagoya was the best.
Thank you very much.
Is it OK?
Yes, it is.
So, tonight's drinking party is...,
Congratulations on getting a job, Sis!
Thank you for always supporting Hana, Sis.
Unlike Hana, you're a strong person, so I knew you'd be fine,
Thank you for your hard work in finding a job.
Congratulations on finding a job!
Congratulations to all of you.
Congratulations on getting a job!
Well, well, well, well... I guess I'll just applaud for now.
I'm sure it's a very happy thing to applaud for the time being,
This is called Ameshiabe,
I feel that "Ameshiabe" involves the celebrations of Kojima prefecture.
In this book, it's a special commemoration of Hana Papa's bedtime,
Bedtime?
Promotion!
Promotion Special.
I fell asleep.
You only put the table in there.
That way?
This way.
Stop it.
Can we do a special on HanaDaddy's successful diet?
Mom will get mad... so we'll say "diet success" like he's failing right now.
You're not on it now, are you?
I'm not.
Then it doesn't matter.
Well, well, well.
But Kojima Prefecture is really like a pilgrimage for candy shiave.
If my sister got a job, of course I would congratulate her.
But it's great to get a job, isn't it?
Isn't it amazing?
It's great.It's amazing.
Because, hey, think about it.
We're working in an office like this,
We're in the entertainment business,
But you never know what's going to happen tomorrow,
You never know what will happen tomorrow.
There are no guarantees.
Our fans are supporting us like this,
That's why we are where we are,
It's not just because of our fans' support, right?
That's right.
So to be honest, we are unemployed.
Well, yes.
To be frank,
If it weren't for our fans, we wouldn't be able to do what we do,
To be honest, it's like being unemployed.
I mean, now that I think about it,
Before going to school, just because I was hungry,
I also started to think that there was no way I could stop by a store before going to school just because I was hungry.
I also thought it was unthinkable to go to the front of the staff room and go home.
Yeah, it's impossible. It's impossible.
I thought about it in a normal way.
It's really impossible for both of us.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, sorry, sorry.
I get it, there's no way we're going to go in the fourth period, have dinner, and then go home.
No way.
It's not possible to leave home in time and not make it home in time.
It's impossible for all of you.
I really think it's impossible.
Please introduce me to the person in charge of recruitment at Stardus Promotion right now.
Please do.
If you can make the position available to us.
If possible, I would like to be a manager of Jikkensen.
Please give me a job.
Then, I'll be in charge of eating Momokuro-san's meals together.
Then, I'll bring Mr. Nagano Main's rice to his mouth.
Then, please take care of me.
I'll be the baggage handler for Mr. Eat Aturo.
Shut up! You're not unemployed!
What?
I'm talking about what you want to dream about.
We're not unemployed.
Our job is to light up the world with our smiles and singing voices.
It's our mission to make it rain happy rain, full of dreams and hopes.
And yet, those of you who say you might be unemployed are not doing your best to be idols?
How about you, Ichika?
No, I'm working hard as an idol.
Aira, you are the center of the group.
I'm going to turn you into a god.
I'm sorry, I think this is my regular job.
Don't make fun of Kamite.
I'm doing it right.
How about Kojiman?
Don't make fun of Kamite.
I'm doing it without gratitude.
Yes, I finally became a professional.
All right!
Let me say this to all three of you.
Human rights for Kamite.
Human rights for Kamite as well.
You guys, I got a job at Raindrops.
Don't forget that feeling that the four of us swore.
Yes, sir.
Then say it firmly one by one.
I'm Hana Kojima, who got a job at Amefureashi.
I'm Aira, who also got a job at Ame-Fureashi.
I'm Ichika Izumiki, who also got a job at Ame-Fureashi.
Hey, Senyaku-san, please help me out.
I am hoping to get a job with you. I'm Shigeka Suzuki.
What is it?
I don't understand.
What kind of a farce is this?
What kind of farce?
It's like you keep putting that in every time.
Are you laughing at me?
Is that what this is all about?
What do you mean?
500 people are watching this crap right now, and I am so embarrassed by this stupid show.
What's going on?
That's why I cut it out and just said the part where he made fun of the paper hand.
I really don't like it.
It's a freesauce.
I wish it would stop. I really don't.
I thought I was getting worse every week.
It's like you're smiling because you know you're going to fail.
There are matches where you are doing it while thinking you are heading for failure.
In the first match, I had the spirit of knowing that I had a chance.
But it started to fall apart around Ichika-san's Shushin.
That's the point, isn't it?
That's it.
I often mispronounce words.
Yes, that's it. That's it.
Because of my mistake?
Yes.
That's the point.That's what I meant.
Sorry, I made a mistake.
Don't do that.
I'm fine!
It's not broken, it's not broken.
It's not off.
No, no, no, no.
I'm fine! I'm fine!
Don't be sleepy.
It's like, "If you're going to apply this script, don't be sleepy.
Yes, it's cute.
It's cute.
Super cute.
He was really indecisive.
So indecisive.
Oh, indecisiveness...
You should be depressed.
It's not good to keep making mistakes.
I'm sorry, it's really everyone's fault.
I'm sorry, it's my fault.
Don't be sleepy!
Oh, that's just a copy of your stuff.
You should do something with everyone.
That's because it's from Airra.
I can only follow the lines.
Oh, that's right. They can't do it without a script.
So if you have a script, you can do it?
Yes, that's right.
That's great. If that's the case, it's amazing.
I can only grow.
There's nothing but room for growth.
For my sister who loves Moka so much.
I collaborated with her to celebrate her finding a job and Moeka's hair loss.
Can I leave a message for Moeka?
Yes, I do. Congratulations on getting a job, Moeka's big sister!
Congratulations!
That's amazing!
That's really great, isn't it?
I have nothing but gratitude for my sister.
You know, on Twitter, she writes introductions for everyone.
I often write those.
That's just...
The group.
Of the group.
And yes-no teaching decisions.
Yes. And so on.
But there are times when I have a bit of a problem with that, Aira.
It's like everything is a slip. Slip equals aira.
That's exactly right.
She made me a character.
She really loves Moeka.
It's hard to believe that she's the same age as me.
I don't think so.
He's always so amazing that I can't believe we're the same age.
Please continue to love AmeFlash.
Congratulations!
I'm good with Moehana-chan's flashes.
I heard you're a moeka-chan moe face master.
That's right.
She called me a moekaeshi.
For me, I have the image that you don't talk to Moehana's sister the most.
That's true.
I want an idol.
But it's still true. Even if she talks too much.
Maybe I like her because she doesn't talk.
If he talks, I might like him a little.
Stop it!
Stop it.
If you talk, he might say, "Ahh!
Then don't talk.
Jesus, I feel like Hana's sister treats me worse than she treats her sister.
Stop saying yes!
I'm saying that because she treats me worse than she treats Hana.
It's true that I'm treated badly at home too.
Stop saying it at home too!
I might have been told that at home too.
That's already a bad word.
Can I ask you to say it in front of him?
Good luck.
Thank you very much. If you are looking for a job, please do your best.
Please do your best.
So, for those of you who are watching the show, if you have anything you want Moehana to get pissed off about, please send it to us here.
If you have anything you want Moehka to get mad about, please tweet it to us using the hashtag Meshatabe and the hashtag Moechin ga okake.
Something may happen on your behalf. Thank you very much.
It won't happen, Moehana.
It doesn't have to happen.
Moehka might get angry.
I will not get angry.
Well, so last weekend, there was a public radio recording and an expedition to Aichi Prefecture.
You went to Takanami.
KP.
Two days of raging.
It was two days of raging, wasn't it?
Yes, it was.
It was the second time for us to record for the radio, so there were people we didn't know before,
They got used to it, and they were excited to join in the fun with us.
They were very good at adding their voices.
One of them even had all of us together.
I think that recording a radio show in public is a different feeling from doing it with just the four of us.
It's great to be able to joke around with everyone,
But when we were in the booth with the four of us, we couldn't joke around with the audience while they were streaming in.I can no longer joke around in the middle of a stream of customers when I'm in that booth with those four people.
I'm sure. It's terrible. I can't show it.
But that's part of it.
It's fun.
It feels like a proper radio recording.
And since everyone is a blabbermouth, it's nice to have them butt in.
I really do.
But there is also a "fun party.
That's great, too.
This time we played a game where balloons exploded,
That was amazing.
It was scary.
For those who don't understand,
The balloons were set to blow up in 40 seconds,
Everyone had to come up with a problem,
For example, each person had to say a four-letter word,
You never know who's going to break it when you put it in their hand. The game.
It was a terrible explanation.
Nice try. Not today. This is no good.
It's a game where you play with balloons that can break at any time,
I was so scared that I fell down.
I didn't fall over. I was knocked over.
It was more of an explosion than the balloons.
Just one person.
You see the bruises?
One right here.
But I didn't.
Bruised.
I don't bruise. My body.
It's strong.
Why did you call it a birthmark?
I thought it would worry you.
I'm fine. Ilan's fine.
He's the same as always.
You never have a bruise, do you?
Once.
I got a big bruise.
It was fun.
The "fun party" is also a project that is held at open recordings and other events,
If you have never been to one of these events, I hope you will come and join us.
The next one is coming up.
It will be on July 2.
Please come and join us on July 2.
Please come.
Can I just ask you to apologize in advance?
Ilan had a bad fall, and I thought, "Oh my God, poor Ilan, he's going to be okay,
I thought he was going to be okay, but he held it until the very last second, 38 seconds,
He had it until the last minute, 38 seconds, and then he had a flash of inspiration and said, "I'm going to pass it to the next person,
Please apologize to the next person.
Ilan, please assume that you are the one who exploded.
Raise your hand.
Apologize.
Victim.
July 1st.
Victim. That's not true.
I'm sorry.
I got banged up the moment I crossed the street.
What am I supposed to do?
Poor guy, but Ilan's more squeamish than you, so you're supposed to think Ilan's okay.
This place is exploding, you know.
It's a mistake. I'm seriously panicking.
I don't know when I'm going to get off when the thing line comes in front of me, and I'm so panicked that I can't get anything out.
There is a theory that you can stand for 40 minutes in a haera.
It's true.
It's difficult. That game.
It was fun.
I'd like to play it at Amechare.
I want to.
Sorry, it was July 1st. I hope you all have a great time.
I'd be happy if you challenge me. Please do.
And thank you for the Aichi satellite.
We had high expectations, didn't we?
Can I say something in the morning? I've never been to Nagoya by plane before.
Aichi, Aichi.
First time?
Yes, I flew there.
I'm so thankful.
I'm really grateful.
It doesn't happen very often.
So we got off the plane, you know, the floor-licking plane.
I saw it for the first time. I thought it must be like this.
There weren't that many people. I guess not many people get on airplanes. From Tokyo to Nagoya.
So you go there in the summer.
That's amazing, isn't it?
That's what surprised me.
I was surprised from the morning.
But first, there was the Lily Way,
But it was raining.
Rain was frustrating.
I wanted it to be sunny,
But even though it was raining, there were so many people.
I was so happy that people who always support me said, "I'll go with you even though it's raining,
I was very happy that people who always support me said they would go with me even though it was raining, and I was very thankful,
I was also grateful to the people who came at the beginning of the event, even though it was raining.
It was great.
But I felt like yesterday was the only day in Aichi.
It was the first satellite event for Lilyway.
It was Lilyway's first satellite event, wasn't it?
I was really happy that many of my relatives came to the event, too,
I only saw it on TikTok,But isn't it amazing that they just saw it on TikTok?
It's amazing that people come to visit us even though they only saw us on TikTok.
Recently, I've had to choose between two options when it comes to my relatives.
TikTok or Omeshabe.
This?
I'm the same way.
That's why I was so surprised.
I guess that's why.
I want people to see it if possible.
I really do.
But I'd like people to see her on TikTok, and then see her on Omeshabe,
I like his personality,
I like her personality.
He has a good personality.
It's a show that has lost a lot of stock, though.
The comments section is also coming from Omeshabe.
Right?
Like 618 people are watching.
The favorability that went up over the weekend may go down on Monday.
I'm not going to stop.
They are supposed to be going down, but they are still coming.
And then there's the person who said, "I've never seen Omeshabeshika before.
What do you mean?
He said he saw it on YouTube and came,
I told him it was the one where they dance,
No, it's something we all know from afar.
That's what brought you here?
What? He was like, "Oh, yeah.
Ichikan-san is a good talker.
So I wondered if he came to me,
He said, "No, I went to everyone.
Oh, no, no, no, no.
Like, "Oh, no, no, no, no, no.
It's true.
If it was raining, I'd have to go.
I'm happy, right?
I'm glad you're coming.
Thank you very much.
I'm watching the show in the rain, sweating.
Oh, I'm soaked.
It's the sweatiest I've ever been.
I was the sweatiest I've ever been.
Where was it? The venue.
Especially the 4 molds.
Let's go with 4 molds and tame.
Can you do it with a lick?
I really can't.
You don't write?
That's a mess.
But you know what? I can totally write with it.
I can do it. I'm sure I put "to-me" on it.
But isn't that what it's called?
No? Names?
What? No?
Focus?
Make sure you know where you're going.
Yuzo, tell the customers to lick the chicken and go home.
I'm sorry, I don't understand. Just use hiragana.
No, you can't.
What was that? I don't know.
It's exactly the same.
Are you sure you can write?
But some people have antennas...
Some people have a rounded one above that.
I see.
But I can totally write this.
I think so.
Confident?
I'm confident.
It's rare.
I mean...
You're lickety-split, aren't you? No, what if I'm wrong?
Is that Kaga's signature or something? No, it's not.
That's why I used hiragana. The form is right.
Is the form correct? No, no.
The form is right. The form I have in mind is right.
Okay, then. You look like you have a Kansai accent.
The form is right.
Shall we start with Ms. Aida?
Got it? You got it, right?
No, me neither.
Shall we go with Ms. Suzuki?
You're not together?
I'm with you. We're the same.
We're definitely on the same page.
Then, Kojima-san.
Oh, I shouldn't do that.
Okay, Miki.
KOKOKEI!
Miki, many times I could write the right letter.
That's great. I can write. That's great.
Why that, why this.
Yomor, kokkei.
Kokey is a way of life, isn't it?
Aim, these two in the middle are right.
Yay!
No, no, no, this is...
No, it's too close.
3B, maybe it's not a push or something.
3B, it's not like I'm pushing or anything... I can't name the venue that has been helping me since I was a genia.They can't name the venue they've been helping me with since 3B Genia.
The Chinese characters are the hardest for me.
You guys are finished. Go home, go home.
I'm lost.
I'm sure there were customers who asked you to leave using the Lilly Belle kanji.
No, there wasn't. They weren't there.
He didn't come to me.
He wasn't there.
They weren't there.
Okay, Mr. Kurase, I have two more ideas for this Kamite and Shimote,
The rest is as the title says. I'm looking forward to working with you.
I'm making the most boring mistake.
How many years has it been?
How long has it been?
How long has it been? A fan said.
About six or seven years?
About five years.
Five years ago was right after I became an Amefura member.
Six or seven years?
Seven years.
I got a spacha.
It's from Mr. Bear.
I became a fan when I saw Isla's video.
I am also a fan of Amefurakko.
I couldn't go to the Jomei event but I watched your video.
Thank you for your hard work.
If you ever do another event in the Kansai area, I hope I can spare some time to go see you.
Good luck to everyone.
Thank you.
I was only able to make it to Aichi for this re-release,
I hope to see you in Shiga, Gifu, and other places in the vicinity,
Shiga or Gifu?
Yes, Gifu.
And Shizuoka.
There were many people from that area.
They came because they are close to us.
I am glad.
I'm glad they came from Aichi, which is 3 hours away.
It made me happy and made me want to visit more people.
I really want to visit more people.
It would be nice if we could go on tour again.
I want to visit various places.
I want to visit many places.
I get a lot of DMs asking me to come.
I really want to go.
I don't have a house where I only do the transparent version,
I want to go to Hokkaido,
I want to go to Hokkaido and other places.
Please wait for me.
I'm glad to see newcomers here this time,
I'd like to go to various places,
I hope you like Amefurashi forever,
I hope that you will always love Amefurashi,
I want you to love Amefurashi so much that you will travel to various places with us,
I hope you will support us so much that you will travel to many places and make many memories with us.
Please do that.
After that, you performed on stage at Mist Fest.
Yes, it was a great experience.
Your dressing room was gorgeous.
It really was.
It was amazing.
No, it wasn't. When we went to the venue, we weren't talking about that.
We were surprised that they started by talking about the backstage.
We wondered if we were allowed to say that.
It's not subtle.
It was a gorgeous dressing room.
I'll shut up for once.
Are you okay? This.
I said it!
I'm so grateful,
It's huge, with mirrors and sofas.
When we entered the venue, there was a reception area,
I asked where our dressing room was,
They told us it was the Bip Room,
What? They all said, "What?
So we could watch the live performance all the time.
What is the Bip Room?
Thank God.
It's a beautiful place with chandeliers.
The moment we entered the backstage, we all dived on the sofa.
Yay!
Let's go to sleep! I said, "Let's sleep!
There was so much food.
We didn't have lunch during lunch time.
So, backstage...
We ran out of food in Japan.
Well, I don't have to tell you this!
We went backstage and kept saying we were hungry.
And then, various staff members
Then, various staff members thought that they should buy food for Ayumi.
So instead of everyone going together, they all went to buy food separately.
The staff members.
They all took care of each other and went to buy the food for Ayumi-chan.
First, we got tenmusu, inari and meisen sandwiches.
Then there was a taco rice bento.
It was at the venue.
We ate that too.
And then the staff!
Since I was close to my hometown, my mother came to the event and brought me a lot of goodies.
They were so delicious.
Shin-chan bought us a lot of fries and nuggets from McDonald's afterwards.After that, Shin-chan bought us a bunch of fries and nuggets from McDonald's.
L size for all of us. It was like the best.
When there were fries and nuggets, they were all except for the D size.
I ate all of them.
It was delicious.
How many pounds did you weigh after that?
About 7 kilos.
And without MC.
Everyone was already inside with nuggets and fries.
The sound of the fryer was amazing.
The sound of the fryer was really bad. It was wobbling all the time.
It was all mixed together.
It was really weird. It was really bad.
Do you have any adjustments?
No. I didn't think it was going to be like this.
I really didn't think it would be like this, and when I was standing there, I thought I was full.
I ate and ate.
I was so full when I danced.
It came out right after we ate.
We should have been careful.
As long as our stomachs were full.
We were careful.
We were careful. We were really careful.
We were a little careful, but it was a feast.
I ate a little bit of everything.
I had the whole desk, even though it was so big.
It was pretty big.
The couch got cluttered quickly with your movements.
I'm sure of it.
No, it wasn't.
It was very clean.
We like to keep things clean.
I really can't show it to you.
It's a serious no-no. This is a serious no-no.
I'm sorry.
It was great.
I was happy.
I had some heavenly food,
I ate super again.
It was delicious.
But I don't know, I've been seeing a lot of Lily Bell and Satsuka lately,
Fest Fest was without Satsuka,
It's been a while since I've had a live show where I couldn't see my cell phone.
It was just so much fun. And since it was in a fairly spacious wind room, I was happy that everyone was dancing so much.
I thought it was really exciting.
But it was also fun that there was no Satsuka at the benefit party.
When there are satsubas, you tend to focus on them,
So I was glad to see that they were enjoying the show with us.
Thank you to everyone who stayed until the end.
I'm sure everyone had to work today, right? Or at school, or whatever.
I'm glad you stayed until the last minute.
Thank you very much.
When we talked about going home, it was during the production of our function,
We were filming all day long.
We were filming.
So I would like to talk about the return trip,
I would like to tell you about my return trip, but I think I'll get to that in the Ame-chare section,
So I'll leave it here for now.
I'm not sure if I'm going to put it out or not, though I've been to the restroom alway.
Oh, no!
No?
Do you want me to let you out?
I was surprised.
Please look forward to it.
I think we have to do it. It's a great opportunity.
It's true.
Always powerful.
If I tell you here, I'll spoil it for you.
Yes, it is.
It was fun.
Spacha is here. From Miss Tsujino,
Thank you for coming to Nagoya. It was fun.
Thank you very much.
But there was one thing that made me really happy,
You know the location of the benefit event was a bit far from the venue of Mist Fest, right?
You had to walk there.
Ayapachi was wearing a denim outfit, right?
Then, after we passed by, a young guy came up to us,
Ha! And they looked at us like we were those girls.
And they looked like those girls.
I heard it from the staff.
From the manager.
Seriously.
Because they were going around in denim costume pick talks.
Are they easy to recognize?
That's great.
I've been trying to get noticed lately,
I've been wearing denim all the time.
Denim at the nearest station.
Denim, denim, denim.
Wouldn't you?
It's mild, right? I'm just trying to be found.
I wanted to be found,
You say in your book, "I'm rooting for you," like you've been approached.
We don't have it yet.
Well, maybe. Let's do it.
Denim, denim, denim.
Let the customers tell you where to buy.
I really think this will change.
I think it will change.I think it will change.
Ira was on the train the other day wearing denim and a white T.
She was wearing no clothes.
Then you were wearing denim.
I'm sorry about that.
It's probably because I'm Ira, regardless.
I'm sorry.
It really wasn't denim.
It was really a denim day.
Chiwaya-san is amazing, isn't he?
He said he was noticed even though he was wearing only denim and a T-shirt and was not wearing any clothes.
That's not what I meant.
I can't go out without makeup, and I wear 100% makeup every day.
I go full-on denim.
Still zero.
O'Laila is really like this, should I study Japanese?
And...
What are you going to start writing?
I don't know. The person next to me suddenly starts writing something I don't understand.
It's like a code.
That's not what I mean.
Denim.
I see.
But, you know, you can't always wear denim all the time.
I can't wear denim forever.
I'm going to try my best to wear denim again.
That's why I'm going to try to wear denim again.
Like denim, then blue denim.
Or a different color denim.
Or pink denim.
Which one?
Denim forever.
I like denim.
It's okay, though.
I do think blue, autumn, and pink denim are cute.
That's all right.
It's true.
There are only a few days left for this release.
There are many events in which we will perform.
I'd like to take a moment to make an announcement.
Here it is.
Oh!
Bye-bye!
Tomorrow?
I'll be on Shake Up Wallop.
Here you go. Thank you very much.
I'll be with Hari-chan.
And, what a surprise, I'd like to set up a three-shot of Hari and Yuzu for tomorrow's benefit.
Seriously?
If there are those who are interested in this, please let me know. If there are people who like that.
I wonder if there are any.
I wonder if there is.
If there are people who would like to have a three-shot with Hari-chan and Yuzu-chan, please come and join us.
I think there are a lot of senior Wallop members at the Wallop meeting this time,
I'm sure there will be a lot of talk machines, so please come and have fun.
Even Yuzu needs to be properly trained, because Hari is also a talker.
That's right. But Hari is great, too,
I met Kiyochi the other day, and he talks a lot.
I also met Satoharu-san, who is a great talker,
When it comes to meetings where people talk, it seems like everyone is machine-gunning the whole time.
But I'm sure it will be a very rare meeting.
I'm looking forward to it.
I'd love to have you.
The day after tomorrow, right?
Yes! We Wednesday, June 14, 22:00 to 23:55, day of the live broadcast.
We will be appearing on Tokyo FM School of Rock.
Yay!
Isn't this great?
This is really great.
School of Rock, right?
People who love the radio.
I've been listening to it ever since I was a student, when I was an adult.
The fans were so happy.
Oh my God.
Why can't I talk?
You have to talk.
I have to talk on the radio.
All the time.
Radio doesn't sell by face.
You mean we have a chance?
Here it comes! Our chance!
What do we do?
The second one from the right, you can't hear him very well, but he has a great voice.
The one who talks all the time doesn't have a good voice.
Worse.
Are there listeners like that?
Is there anyone like that?
No, I don't.
She's the worst.
I might be able to get so many listeners that I might even get some comments like, "That's a good idea.
I agree.
Let's try to come together!
I'm sure you're right.
The next one is in July.
Please listen to us.
On June 23rd, there will be a perfume probability 100% Happier MechaFest!
This time it's Yuzu and Hana.
For the first time as a pair.
Hana-chan for the first time.First time, Hana-chan.
Let's cook.
It's always been Mo Hana, Yuzu.
That's right.
It's always been Hana.
All flowers.
All flowers?
All moehana.
Only Yuzu didn't do it.
I see.
Then you've done all the Hana.
All done.
Then it's Hana and someone else.
But I'd feel safer if Hana was here.
That's for sure.
No one has failed yet.
Let's try not to fail at all.
Applications will be accepted until June 16.
Sounds fun. Pink in Yuzu Flowers.
I will be performing solo at an event called Acoustic Night Fantasy on Tuesday, July 4.
It says acoustic, so I'm doing Acoustic Night Fantasy, so I'll be doing Acoustic Night Fantasy.
There will be other idols as well, so there will be a total of five of us.
So I think fans from various places will come,
It will be at DUO MUSIC EXCHANGE.
It starts at 6:30pm.
Tickets are now on sale and will be available until July 3,
I would be very much encouraged if you could all come and support us.
Is this an event called Fantasy?
Does this mean that Sukkah Cafe Fantasy is going to be fun-fun-fun-fun after all these years?
Fantasy?
Did you hear that?
Don't be fooled by fantasy.
This is rare.
I didn't listen to it.
You're all alone.
It's a little awkward.
I hate it.
I'm not alone.
I have a script.
And there's Daichan and Himeyaki.
All the things are done by all of us.
Well, there have to be three of us, at least.
That's right.
He said he would do it someday.
That's enough.
Yes.
So, it's a no-fantasy song.
No fantasy. Sorry.
That's sad.
I am singing a no-fantasy song.
I'm sorry, but I don't want to upload it.
You decide what songs you want to sing because there are so many, don't you?
Yes, I do.
I decide everything, even the MC.
I make requests, but they never match.
It's so difficult.
But if Aira makes a request, I can do it.
Sorei Campan, too.
Sorei Campan too.
I don't want to do it anymore.
I thought that if I made a request, everyone would sing something.
I thought they would sing something for me.
I don't know.
Okay, one, two, three, four, Precure!
Pre-cure! Pre-cure! Pre-cure! Pre-cure! PreCure! PreCure!
Precure! I want you to do it.
It's really bad. You guys should think about it.
I don't know what I'll do.
I know, but I want you to do a field day type song too.
Ah.
Burn Burn Burn Burn Burn Burn Burn Burn Burn Burn Burn Burn Burn Burn Burn Burn Burn Burn Burn Burn Burn Burn Burn Burn Burn Burn Burn Burn Burn Burn Burn Burn Burn Burn Burn Burn
Sorry, we're down 100.
Yikes!
I'm sorry, we're down by 100.
I'm sorry, I'll confess next time.
Next time is fine, July 15th.
On July 15, I will be performing at an event called Spark 2023.
It's going to be at Lake Yamanaka, and I'm really looking forward to it.
You can see Mt. Fuji. We will all take pictures like this in front of Mt.
But it's been changed, so it's past June 8.
So if you can come, let's have fun together.
And I will be performing at Lucky Fest on July 17.
I'm so happy!
It's going to be held at a place called Kyokunaga Kita Senchu Kaihin Park,
We're surrounded by amazing and gorgeous artists.
There are people singing the songs that we always perform before the festival.
It's not good.
Isn't it bad?
They are singing "Jamboree," "Jakankan," "Jamboree.
It's not good, is it?
I'm really looking forward to it.
It's the same day.
I'll be there with Mr. Dice, and I'll be wearing a new outfit.
I was thinking of wearing a T-shirt.
Oh no! Let's be geeks!
I'm going to sing "Yukigetsukanohana" and other songs.
I'll also do "Golden Sourdough" and rap at all.
If that's the case, I'm pretty much on fire.
It's like, "I'm here to listen to you, but then who starts singing?
It's his own fault for suddenly stepping up on stage and stepping out.Suddenly I'm up on stage and stepping out, and it's my fault.
It's kind of a towel, me.
That's how much I'm looking forward to it.
Please, by all means, please support Anamehra.
And on July 18,
I will be performing at the 3rd annual Itto Hisshin Dai Zan Special Kuuken Tournament.
Woo! Go for it, go for it!
Yes, let's see, Musashino Performing Arts Theater, a place called Kogekijo, you know?
Little Theater
I will be performing at a place called Little Theater.
Yes, tickets are on sale now. We're going to do a big slash.
You are going to do your best as an idol among comedians, aren't you?
Go for it!
Please give my best regards.
I'll be rooting for you.
I'm still going to start the daily depths, aren't I?
Let's work hard for this.
Think it's just a word.
Last.
I will send you a dark story.
So, I will be performing at a festival called "Manga Expo" in Taiwan from July 27th to July 31st.
Taiwan, Taiwan, Tokyo, stick!
Let's eat green onion buns.
Yes, I will.
It was delicious.
This is really our second overseas festival.
We went to Taiwan, and it was a new one called Taiwan-Taiwan Connection.
Taiwan connection.
We are retreating, aren't we?
Taiwan and Taiwan.
Taiwan-Taiwan connection.
It's become "Taiwan-Taiwan".
Oh no.
It's Taiwan-Taiwan connection.
Yes, it is.
So,
So, it looks like the bread tour will be held again,
If you want, let's all go on an expedition together and have fun.
Let's go together.
Please do.
And last but not least,
And the last but not least...,
The final event of our re-leave will be held on June 24th at La Laporte Torres.
It will be the final final of the mini album Coffee's ReLeave,
On this day, we are aiming for 500 consents,
Is that right?
No, it's not.
It's decided. What's a final?
What's the finals?
Final final final...
Hey! Aren't you guys aiming for 500?
We don't have enough to fill up our tanks.
Excuse me, Mr. Suzuki.
I'm sorry. I'm really sorry.
I'm sorry for saying that.
We're definitely going for the 500-release agreement!
Aaah!
I'm really fired up.
Maximum super enthusiasm.
I'm so pumped!
Oh no, we're down 100.
Again? We're down a hundred.
Again?
But you know, I really want you to come. The time is still undecided,
But maybe it will be at a time when everyone can easily come? I don't know.
You can't tell me the time? Not yet.
I can't say.
You can't?
I can't tell you.
It's noon.
LUNCH?
Lunch?
Yes, it is. It's all right.
It's lunchtime.
It's not what you are saying.
If anyone is going to be offended, it will be me.
Yes.
Then say more.
It's already noon.
It's noon.
Oh, yes.
One more time.
Yes.
Easy to come?
Yes, it is. It's a partial system.
Yes. Already.
One more time there.
But, you know, this time, after the usual scoring session, I said, "Thank you.
At the very end.
Encore light.
Wow! After the award show?
After.
Oh~!
Really?
With a loss.
Seriously?
You don't have lunch at any of the sites, do you?
Oh, that's a good question.
Yes, that's a good question.Yes.
Oh, really?
Mr. One Love, it's 2:00 p.m., right?
What? You can't turn around?
I'm not covered!
Yes, you can.
I'm not covered.
I'm not wearing a love handkerchief or anything.
Oh!
One Love is at 3:00 pm.
It's not covered by the 2:00 p.m. event at noon, but yes, it is.
I'm going to live separately for a while during the benefit meeting.
Oh~!
And if you come back again for the encore last encore live or something.
It means it's good.
Hard.
Also, Ukkaplapo is doing a show in the west.
Yes.
We are not covering the time.
Oh!
Just in case.
So, you can see the distribution at all, right?
Oh!
We don't have any overlap.
If everyone who is watching now comes, we will have 500 people.
Yes.
It's wireless. It's wireless. It's free.
It's on the web.
Only on the train to Raraport Toyosu.
I'm sure there are many things to do on the train.
Yes, there are.
When you walk, it's practically wireless.
Yes, I will be able to get there in time if I walk.
If you walk now, you will make it in time.
I really want you to come. Because there are really 550 people watching already.
Yeah.
You know, for all of you who come, you will have something wonderful to remember.
It will stay. I hear it will.
There might be.
I wonder if it's something that will remain as a form.
I'm glad it will remain as a form.
It's not just memories.
All of the above,
The manager is responsible.
We didn't say anything,
We don't say anything, it's all the manager's responsibility.
That's it.
Because our hearts are different.
Because we are a team.
The circumference of your mind is different, right now.
We are a team.
But it's really easier to come here than to a live concert,
It's easier to come than a live concert.
It's like you can go to a show with a light heart.
It's free, so you can go.
We would be happy if people like us here and come to our other paid concerts.
I would like to connect this event to the bio-music industry.
I don't think there will be any free events for a while.
There won't be.
Please do try.
If you come to this Lily, are you a child?
Yes, that's the one from June, right?
The one before June, right?
Yes, that's right.
I would say it's still just barely a rapport.
June 24th is still OK.
June 25th is already bad.
June 5 is a little bit bad.
As I recall.
I think that's what the contract says.
What contract?
Matsuno.
I'll check again later,
I'll check again later, but I think that's it.
I'm fine with the 24th, but not the 25th,
But not on the 25th, right?
I think.
Who came to 624?
Yes, I did.
Three of you.
Please.
And the last one.
This one is important.
Ameflash's one-man live Bio-san 2023
will be held on July 9 in Shinjuku, Tokyo.
This is a part of the show as a sole down,
The remaining two parts of the event are still available, and the buses have stopped.
Oh no.
I wonder how many tickets are left.
Fingers crossed.
Fingers.
Masa-chan.
How many more?
That one.
What?
It's gone down.
Even less.
What?
And even though you told me about it...
Two sheets.
I wonder who's going to buy them.Who will buy it?
I'm glad.
But don't you think? This timing.
No, someone who came to lick it.
People who have seen Amershaven.
But you know what?
I don't think Amershaven has a "kyunbai" effect anymore.
But the person I fell in love with yesterday..,
I think TikTok still has an effect.
I thought it was still there.
Still there?
He said it's still there.
I'm glad.
While I still can.
Oh, man. I'm so happy.
I'm so happy.
We're just a few more steps away.
Rumor has it that if only this were the case.
I'll be able to become a Mr. and Mrs.
Wow.
Oh, so contractually, the 24th is fine.
The 25th is not.
But if you come on April 9...
I heard that the contract says that you can come on the 25th.
That seems to be the contract.
Anything is possible.
No, no, no, no, but
After that, it's no good.
It's tough.
Only here.
Absolutely.
Not before July 9, but only on July 9.
I'm sure you'll say it at the end of the year or at some other concert.
I won't say it.
I'm not going to say anything.
If you come to this year-end concert, it will be Mr. Child.
No, I'll confirm it later.
I think that was the agreement.
I think so.
That's my contract.
But you never know what will happen in this world.
Things are always changing.
That's true.
Well, then, Mr. Child.
This is the way it is now.
I don't think people want you that badly.
That's not it. No, I don't.
You want it, don't you?
You want it, don't you? I want to be a child.
I want it.
We are looking forward to seeing you all.
Thank you very much.
I've lost my spacha.
One person, Mr. Yahu.
I'm waiting. Like Ibaraki.
I'm waiting in Ibaraki.
The other one disappeared before I could open it anymore.
The other one, Akashin-san, is sending me a cute stamp.
Wan wan.
Thank you very much.
Kakuteike-san, I became a fan 4 days ago.
Please continue to be addicted to me.
If you come on the 24th and the 9th, you'll be a child.
She came yesterday.
Really? Then you're a child.
Mizuna-san. This is what Moeka-chan read out at the beginning of the show.
I usually only stand in line for the Yuzu benefit event, but I'm going to thank Moeka-chan.
No, I can't. I have to go to the Yuzu line.
Of course I will go to the Yuzu line.
That's fine.
I might come to Moeka's line and become a Moeka-chan fan.
I didn't write it.
Thank you very much.
If it was a betrayal, I might become a Moeka guesser.
I didn't write it.
Thank you very much.
I'm sorry that one more person couldn't read it.
I'm sorry.
Thank you very much.
I didn't write the other one.
Please write him inside.
In your imagination.
Imagine.
It says something like, I love candy flash.
That's the one where Moeka said she loved it, and I wanted to have a flow where everyone was like, "I love Moeka.
It said I love Moeka.
Heh.
Eh, tsukkomi.
Don't say it with a smile. I didn't want to be tsukked.
I'm sorry. Thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
And, at the end of this Ameshabe, there will be a big announcement.
It's a little bit dangerous.
Are you okay?
It's not good.
It's time for the big announcement.
Everyone, please make sure you watch to the end.
Please do.Please.
It's not like we should skip the next corner for that big announcement.
Let's skip it.
This week's uniform.
It's the best project of the day.
It's already the best.
That's right.
It's already the best section.
Uniform of the week.
I don't think so.
Can I at least have them do it?
I'm the most insta-follow scribe right now, so can I ask you to do your best?
So, I would like you to make the most of this week's uniforms.
It's the best follower scribe right now.
Shall we do it? This.
We have to get 3,000 people.
Do you want to do it? Do it? This one.
Our goal is to get 3,000 people today.
That's right.
Then, let's do it.
We had a lot of first-timers at the Tokomame event.
So I think there are people who are watching this distribution for the first time today.
That's right.
This is the second time for us to have such a corner to let people get to know us better.
This is the second time.
The name is "Nice to meet you! I am Yatsuki Ichikawa.
This is for those who have recently joined us and those who have been supporting us for a long time.
I hope all of you will get to know us.
This is an in-depth project featuring each and every member of AmeFlash.
This time it's Yuzu-chan.
Thank goodness! I was afraid that the project would be lost because the previous recipient ended up like that.
What does that mean?
I don't know what to say.
I'm sorry, I can't cover it.
It was awful.
But I'm glad it's not gone.
I mean, you got it, the project.
I'm glad.
Yes, but I'd like to feature Yuzu this time to convey its charm.
Please come in!
Okay, I'll start again. Nice to meet you! I am Yatsuki Ichikawa.
Well, my name is Yatsuki Ichikawa.
I was born on November 2, 2003.
I am a scorpion-lizard, type A, in the year of the sheep.
This is the first time I know.
That's how it is.
So that's how it is, huh?
Let's see, my favorite food is...
Oooooh!
Eh, it's not like that.
Why, you know, when it was my time, everyone started joking around.
When it was Moeka's time, they were like, "Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I'm sorry, I don't have time for this...
Wow, that's great. I didn't let them introduce themselves.
Oh, wow. There were 600 or so people here a while ago, and now there are 490...
That's why I'm pushing so hard, everyone's gone to their rooms when I say it.
That's right.
We're doing this now at a very unfavorable time, yuzu.
They're doing it when we're down 100 to 100.
Yuzuki, I want you to look at the other Yuzuki.
It's true. I'm at a huge disadvantage.
Please, what's your favorite food...
Ooooo!
Ta-da!
That's enough.
Natto and...
And lean meat.
Red meat.
Gyukke, basashi...
Basashi... you seem to like it.
I like it a lot.
I like sweets, and macaroons.
Yes, I do.
I also like anything and everything.
Like okra.
Yes, I like okra.
Hirai's food is rounded-off square stew.
What, rounded off...
Why can't I eat shikakuni?
But you know, Momokuro-san is often at a food stall...
When Momokuro-san is at a live food stall, he likes Kakuni Mann.
Momo Kakuni Man is the only one I can eat.
In Kakuni.
It was delicious.
I don't mind Kakuni Man, but not Kakuni.
I don't know, my hobbies are...
But I guess I like to talk with people.
That's for sure.
I have an image of talking all the time.
I have a hard time with silence,
I feel the urge to talk, so I talk all the time.
That's true.
I find myself on the phone with someone all the time.
Calling?
You're on the phone.
In front of everyone?
You do it sometimes.
You're on speaker and you're talking to your mom or something.
You call them and say "hello".I'll be around, if you'll have me.
You should be careful who you call Yuzu.
You better get round and round.
I'll put them all on speaker.
Because Yuzu doesn't get it anymore.
It's all on speaker.
It's so cute when he says hello.
It's so annoying.
Friends and family, put them all on speaker.
I want to call them while I'm preparing something.
Do they know you're on speaker?
I don't know.
I feel sorry for you, I really do.
I feel so bad for them.
They put us through this ordeal of not knowing when or if it's going to happen.
I don't know what that means.
They're talking all the time, even in stuff like stafframento.
Yes, they do.
Igina-chan and Uka-chan are very talkative, so they probably talk a lot.
I also talk with Kurapo-chan all the time.
What do you like about beauty?
I like all things beauty-related,
I also like anime.
I often watch cartoons in between lessons.
During break time, even though it's not even 5 minutes, I'm sure I open my phone and watch it during break.
What are you into now?
Anime?
Recently, I've been watching "The Chef.
It's super long. I don't know what it's called.
It's a very long one.
If you reincarnate.
When the cook reincarnates.
Like a slime?
There's that too.
If you reincarnate, you become a cook.
Like if a cook reincarnates?
What do you mean?
Anime, cooking.
Different world.
You've been into that lately?
Otherworldly.
He's been into otherworldly stuff lately.
He's been into "Otherworldly Good News Rou-Son?
I've been into that recently.
I've watched all of them.
Also, I'm looking at all the manga about Oshi no Kome.
Oshinokome.
I've seen the latest one on Jump Plus.
But I'm sad that I can't talk about it with you guys, so I want you all to watch it later with me.
Oshinoko.
I'm interested in Oshinoko too. It's amazing.
You should see it.
You'd be surprised by TikTok, but you're just a know-it-all.
And if she's an idol, you should definitely watch it.
I've seen it up to the middle. It's a manga.
My mom is really into it and recommended it to me.
It's an anime that is said to be easy to watch even for kids who don't like anime,
Also, the pictures of the anime are really cute.
I want to watch it.
It's easy to watch.
I want to start watching it tonight.
Please watch it.
Oshiko.
I love the cartoons and the mentor-tainment section and everything.
I love it.
That's all.
Is that all?
That's all for Yuzu's self-introduction by Yuzu.
Would you like to introduce your past?
Yes, I do.
You are of course a very cute looking girl,
She looks like a gal, but she is also good at talking,
But she is also a good talker,
She is very funny.
I say this because I am a member.
I'm a member.
That's right.
It's very interesting.
Even in the dressing room, we are a little bit,
I'm so tired today,
When we are feeling like we can't take it anymore,
Ichikawa would do something to make us laugh.
So it is different if we come to a scoring session and ask him to do something funny.
That's not right.
That's different.
It's an attack on Yuzu,
It's like they laugh at you because you are a member.
Like that change of clothes over there.
What, what, what, what?
What did you do? What did you do?
That's not fair.
Oh, that's nice.
I like it.
You know what? It's fine.
Oh, my God, I'm depressed.
I'm quite sensitive.
I was quite sensitive.
Sensitive.Sensitive.
I like it.
Later.
Because I can't say it here later.
I can't say it here.
Well, if it's something interesting that can't be said here, you can't do something interesting at the scoring session.
I can't do that.
Mr. Ichikawa, you only have 0 or 100, really.
Yes, I don't want to show 50 or so to everyone.
I can't show it to you, but I can tell you that it is a very interesting codition.
Thank you very much.
That's what I mean.
It's a very vulgar codition no matter how you hear it.
That may be what I mean.
It's interesting, isn't it?
You are a mood maker, aren't you?
Thank you very much.
Of the rain flash.
Yes, you're right.
I think you are surprisingly knowledgeable.
Knowledgeable?
This is the same for the genre,
But maybe not Japanese at all.
I'm trying to narrow it down, but she is very knowledgeable about beauty,
When I talk to her about my skin problems, for example,
When I talked about my skin problems, for example, she would say, "You should do this," or "Have you tried this? She is always consulting with me,
She always consulted with me,
Once I did that, I was cured,
She also knows a lot about cosmetics and clothes,
He also knows about cosmetics, clothes, etc. He really helped us a lot when we were traveling and doing taiens,
He also knows about cosmetics, clothes, etc. He really helped us with travel and other things,
She takes the lead,
I think she is the person I would most like to have as a girlfriend.
Is that different from that?
Whether or not you want her to be your girlfriend.
Well, she's the best.
Why the nose?
I'd like her to do everything for me,
But I do. I just end up doing it.
I'm the type of person who does everything for others.
I'm the type of person who gives everything to others.
I'm the type of person who gives it all away.
Thank you very much for what you did for us in Thailand.
We can't do anything now,
We can't do anything, we won't do anything.
Don't put us together.
We are the group that can't do anything.
We don't do anything.
We can't do anything.
You can't do it.
You can't do anything even if you try.
But Yuzu is amazing,
She's surprisingly solid.
We were able to buy matching dresses and ice cream together,
Thanks to Yuzu, we were able to go shopping.
If it were up to me, we would only go to the beach.
It's always the ocean.
And then, I'm told one-on-one time at twilight.
One by one, one by one.
Once here, time to be brought together in the twilight.
It is necessary, isn't it?
I might have become.
I need it.
I'm not sure if I'm a yuzu or an airo, but I'm a yuzu.
I think I can turn a little.
I can do a lot of things.
I'm glad.
I'm glad we were able to buy that dress, all of us.
Do you have another one?
I usually act like my own character,
But during live performances and scoring sessions, I think I am very cute and charming.
Cute and cute.
Lately, a lot of fans have been uploading their photos on TikTok.
I see them all on TikTok, and I was like, "Yuzu, you're doing this.
It's pretty much like being an idol.
Yuzu is the idol.
They are very cheeky.
When I came to see them perform live, I was hit with a cap.
The staff members are always asking "What's going on?
Maybe they like idols.
I think they know what they're doing.
I'm glad.
I think it's cute.
I do like yuzu cuteness,
I want everyone to be cute, so I'll probably tell them everything.
Like, "Maybe this one is cuter.
Are you going to tell me?
I think it would be cute if you do it this way.
If you want to raise your self-esteem, this is for you.
It may look like I refuse everything,
Yuzu is surprisingly accepting.
That's for sure.
You're so kind.
Thank you very much.
I'm a little embarrassed.
Super embarrassing.
If you're doing this, you'll understand, but it's super embarrassing.
What should I say?
It'll be fun.
Is my mom going to be okay?Is my mother okay?
It's my turn to go around.
I don't think so.
I need time to think about it, if possible, so have her do it last.
She may not show up next week.
I thought I was doing pretty well for everyone.
I tried my best, but it still hasn't shown up this week.
I didn't do my best enough.
You're right.
I'm sorry.
When you say it like that, it doesn't matter.
Is there anything else you want to do?
I have something.
Let's do one.
I'm sure you're right.
First impression.
Kiz.
I think this one is easy to get.
It's a first impression.
I wrote. It's good.
Yuzu cut.
It's cute.
Thank you.
It's a rabbit.
Like and rabbit.
If you have it, write the first person's name in small letters where it's written.
The first person. This is when the other three of us first met Yuzu,
The first time the other three of us met Yuzu, or when we first met Yuzu, or when we remember the first person's name,
Yuzu will guess how the members write it.
The first person, Yuzu's first person.
Then let's write it.
I think it's all pretty much the same, though, isn't it? This impression.
I guess so.
What? This one?
Oh, that one! I see. That's for sure.
I think so.
First impressions are basically the same for everyone.
I don't think they are basically the same.
It's not the same.
Of course not.
I'm sorry. I said it randomly.
Well, I don't know.
I said it in a random way.
Do you think it's different for you? Everyone is.
But Yuzu is really easy to get into because of her looks.
I see.
OK!
Is it okay?
Okay, I'll go with you.
Then, shall we go together?
Okay. Ready!
Ta-da! From the flowers.
Heavenly and flashy ribbons. A very flashy girl.
Earth magic. And the image of her in a ponytail.
Wow.
Hana, flashy clothes. Ira, flashy clothes. Moka, curly hair.
At first, I was going to make Hana with curly hair. But when I said, "Can't we all do the same thing? I said, "Yes! I said, "Yes!
So, I was wondering if Moka was going to wear the brand or the hair?
I'm sorry if you were wondering, but you've been coming to the brand Earth Magic for a long time.
I'm sure there's an impression of a side ponytail, but I have the image of her wearing a ponytail all the time.
The actual ponytail is a very important part of the look of a person's hair, and it's a very important part of the look of a person's hair.
I wonder if it's her personal clothes... she's really bigger than her face... she wears pink and green type clothes...
And she was wearing a tutu like a sponge.
I used panniers, but they come in all different colors.
So I bought all kinds of mesh tights, pink, light blue, yellow, green, etc.
The top T-shirt is so tiny compared to the huge skirt.
Tiny? It's a little snug and a little long.
I love the bears or the hearts... if you're an Earth magician...
I think you've got most of the Earth magic in there. Yuzu is just the image I have of her.
I didn't expect to get that impression of Yuzu's personality.
I'm sorry, I'm the one who stands out.
But... you were quiet at first.
You were quiet at first.
Aisle-chan! I love Aisle-chan!
I love Aisle-chan.
You're the one who asked me out on a Christmas date. Christmas together is so annoying.
I know it's true... he asked me out on a Christmas date. He used to ask me out.
Ira's clothes were so tacky, he had to leave.
You don't have to tell me that. It must have been really tacky.
She said she was surprised that Rush wore it, and that she got picked up and skirted all over the place.
It was fine, but it wasn't the kind of dress that would get you picked up and skirts all over the place.
I was all black after Yuzu's Christmas date with Isla.
That's a big deal.
I was so embarrassed. She was dressed like a wolf.
What kind of clothes?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. I'm just saying.
The ones with the dancing fur. Those used to be all the rage, but I was just wearing that.
You know, like damaged pants, black skinnies, a white knit, and a down jacket.
It was a bit of an ooh-shah-shah.
I thought, "Let's go a little more flashy for Christmas.
That's great. That's what I'm talking about. She's wearing a skirt.
I thought it was great that she gave me her cell phone number.
I don't want it!
But we were all the same. I had this impression of flamboyance.
She's still flashy, though.
I don't know. But I have an image of her being flashy, too.
But you like colored things, don't you?
I guess it's like this... It's just as everyone thinks.
But if it's really nice to meet you and you don't like to talk...But if you've never met someone before, or if you don't like to chat...
If you go to a Yuzu benefit event, you will never lose track of the conversation, so don't worry about it!
But if there is one thing I have to warn you about...
Don't make a face that looks like you want to leave after they say it's time to go.
Is there anyone like that? It's usually someone who just wants to talk a little longer.
Like, "I think I'm almost done with my preparations," because you can't stop yipping for a second.
It's like you've already been told, so you can go home, so please don't do that.
I think it's a lot of fun. Thank you.
I'd love to see you on Instagram, Twitter, TikTok, etc. Please follow me!
Please do!
I hope you like Yuzu.
I hope you like Yuzu!
So, Yuzu, do you have any last words?
No!
No?
Impossible? Sorry.
You want to try Aya?
No, I'm not going in. I'm not going in.
So that's it. Nice to meet you, I'm AmeFlash. That's it!
And now, for the last part of the show.
This week's Suikun is Suikun, who gets a tulle from his grandma.
This week's Suikun is Suikun getting a tulle from his grandma.
After Ayuzu's self-introduction, we are down to 200 people.
Eat the tulle, Ayuzu.
I'm down over 200 people.
With a change of clothes, on a secret base.
Before you know it, we'll be on a secret base.
Hey, about one more
I'm not crying.
What? What do you mean?
Oh, no, that's good.
Grandma's hand.
You're so clingy. You're so cute.
I'm so cute.
It's just like it always is.
Yes, it is.
No, not that one, the one hanging there.
The house is so dirty. The watermelon in the doggy hammock. It's so cute.
They were hanging like fishermen.
It's like this. It's so cute.
Okay, that's it for this week.
Let's see what you got.
Hmm? We're going to do a spell.
The last one.
Because if we do that one first...
Maybe 50 people will see the spell.
That's fine.
But they don't have to see it.
Then I'll do it first. Finally, I'm going to leave you with the Moe Magic corner, where Moeko will give you a spell to do your best for the week.
Good luck for a week. And lucky you!
I went to Aichi yesterday.
I'll be stuck.
Oh, so you're stuck now even though you're good friends?
You're stuck?
I used it yesterday. I'm stuck.
It's stuck. I can't help it.
Everyone in Aichi is in love with you.
Now, I would like to make a big announcement.
What is it?
Don't stop.
It's okay to say it.
No, no, no, no.
Oh my God, Kojima-san. Don't make me stop!
My contract ends today.
I'm not quitting.
Don't end it!
The contract... Do not terminate!
Calm down.
Maybe I wasn't calm.
It's not that I wasn't calm. It's just a normal contract.
Did they cut you off already?
Something like that.
Well, there's nothing we can do about it.
No, it's not.
I don't have time.
We don't have time.
I laughed.
Okay?
It's really important.
It's a big announcement, guys.
Come on, it's in 40 minutes.
Let's do it right.
In 40 minutes, at 10:00 p.m.!
One Mo Time's music video will be released!
The last one...
I wanted to say that when there were a lot of people around.
When did you shoot it?
I didn't know when I looked.
I couldn't find it yesterday.
It's too early.
Ori schedule.
You should take some candy.
Wow. I went to a festival and shot a music video at Lily Fest.
But it's different and cute again.
Everyone is cute.
It's a different music video than usual.It's a different kind of music video.
It was really cute.
Will you let me continue the one-more-time?
It's nice to see them back in a good mood, isn't it?
It's amazing.
I have to see it.
Rather than the usual bachi bachi Amefura-chan.
I think we'll see a different and new side of Amefurachan.
If you'd like to see it, please come to the show at 10:00 p.m.
Please wait for me.
Spread the word!
Please spread the word in an instant when it goes up at 10pm.
It's a really great music video.
Let's aim for 100,000 views first.
Let's do our best.
Of course, I'd like you to watch it, but I'd also like you to watch Blow Your Mind.
Blow Your Mind, too.
I hope you will move to a new place and watch it again.
Please do.
It might be fun to compare.
Maybe it's the day you want to compare.
Please do.
So please come back to YouTube at 22:00.
Let's all finish together.
Seino.
Let's talk about Ameidolle while Ameidolle is on.
Ameidolle for short.
We'll be there at 22:00 to sing.
Bye bye.